<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.trakt" name="Trakt" version="3.6.1" provider-name="Trakt.tv, Razzeee">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.trakt" version="4.4.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.dateutil" version="2.8.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="defaultscript.py">
        <provides>executable</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" name="trakt.service" library="default.py" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata" name="trakt.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license> GPL-2.0-only</license>
        <forum>https://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=220547</forum>
        <website>https://trakt.tv</website>
        <source>https://github.com/trakt/script.trakt</source>
        <news>- Clarify unit on startup delay
- Migrate to new settings format
- Allow to override global proxy settings
- Fix empty movie title when year not included in showtitle
- Fix runtime fallback for calculating episode and movie progress
- Fix hide notifications when playing video
- Update translations</news>
        <assets>
            <icon>icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
            <screenshot>resources/image-01.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/image-02.png</screenshot>
            <screenshot>resources/image-03.png</screenshot>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="da_DK">Tv- og film-scrobbler til Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">TV und Film Scrobbler für Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="el_GR">Υπηρεσία κοινοποίησης ταινιών και τηλ. σειρών (scrobbler) στο Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">TV and movie scrobbler for Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Scrobbler de Películas y Series para Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="et_EE">Sarjade ja filmide vaatamisoleku sünkroonimine Trakt.tv teenusega</summary>
        <summary lang="fi_FI">Sarjojen ja elokuvien katselutilanteen Trakt.tv-kirjaus</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Scrobbler TV et film pour Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="he_IL">Scrobbler סדרות וסרטים עבור Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="he_IL">Scrobbler סדרות וסרטים עבור Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="hr_HR">TV i filmski skrobler za Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="hu_HU">Sorozat és film beküldő a Trakt.tv-hez</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Scrobbler di serie TV e film per Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="ko_KR">Trakt.tv에 TV와 영화 시청 상태를 전송합니다</summary>
        <summary lang="lt_LT">TV ir filmų registratorius, skirtas Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="nl_NL">TV- en films-scrobbler voor Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="pl_PL">Dodatek umożliwiający rejestrację odtwarzanych i obejrzanych seriali i filmów w serwisie Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_PT">Scrobbler de episódios e filmes para o Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="pt_PT">Scrobbler de episódios e filmes para o Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="sk_SK">Seri</summary>
        <summary lang="sv_SE">TV och film skrobblare för Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="uk_UA">Скроблер серіалів та фільмів для Trakt.tv</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">Trakt.tv的观影打卡器</summary>
        <description lang="da_DK">Scrobble automatisk alle tv-afsnit og film du ser til Trakt.tv! Du får en omfattende historik af alt, hvad du har set og bliver del af et globalt fællesskab af serie- og filmentusiaster. Tilmeld dig gratis på http://trakt.tv og få et væld af funktioner:[CR][CR]- Scrobble automatisk alt hvad du ser[CR][CR]- Mobilapps til iPhone, iPad, Android og Windows Telefon[CR][CR]- Del det, du ser (i realtid), samt send bedømmelser til Facebook og Twitter[CR]- Personlig kalender, så du aldrig går glip af en serie eller film[CR]- Følg med i hvad dine venner og bekendte ser[CR]- Brug huskelister så du ikke glemmer, hvad du skal se[CR]- Vis og imponér din samling til venner[CR]- Opret brugerdefinerede lister[CR]- Hold nemt øje med dit serie-fremskridt i løbet af sæsoner og afsnit[CR]- Sammenlign din samling mod lister fra f.eks. IMDb Top 250[CR]- Opdag nye serier og film baseret på dine tv-vaner[CR]- Widgets til din forumsignatur[CR][CR]Hvad kan dette add-on tilbyde?[CR][CR][CR]- Scrobble automatisk alle tv-afsnit og film, du ser[CR]- Synkroniser dine tv-afsnit og filmsamlinger til Trakt (efter en opdatering af biblioteket)[CR]- Automatisk oprydning af din Trakt-samling, så den passer sammen med Kodi[CR]- Hold set status synkroniseret mellem Kodi og Trakt[CR]- Bedøm film og afsnit umiddelbart efter at de er set[CR][CR]Særlig tak til alle der har bidraget til dette add-on! Se historikken og changelog for at se hvem disse talentfulde udviklere er.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Scrobble automatisch alle Serien und Filme die du schaust zu Trakt.tv! Behalte den Überblick über deine Sammlung und sei Teil einer globalen Gemeinschaft von Serien- und Filmliebhabern. Registriere jetzt deinen kostenlosen Account unter http://trakt.tv und bekomme einen Haufen Funktionen:[CR][CR]- Automatisches scrobbeln von dem was du guckst[CR]- Mobile Apps für iPhone, iPad, Android und Windows Phone[CR]- Teile was du schaust (in Echtzeit) und bewerte auf Facebook und Twitter[CR]- Personalisierte Kalender: So verpasst du nie wieder eine Serie[CR]- Folge deinen Freunden und Leuten, für die du dich interessierst[CR]- Mach dir Beobachtungsliste zu nutze, um nicht zu vergessen was du ansehen wolltest[CR]- Tracke deine Mediensammlung, um deine Freunde zu beeindrucken[CR]- Erstelle benutzerdefinierte Listen zu jedem Thema das dir einfällt[CR]- Behalte die Übersicht über deinen Fortschritt bei Serien[CR]- Überblicke deinen Fortschritt bei offiziellen Listen wie zum Beispiel den IMDb Top 250[CR]- Entdecke neue Serien und Filme anhand deines Geschmacks[CR]- Widgets für deine Forum Signatur[CR][CR]Was kann dieses Addon?[CR][CR]- Automatisches scrobbeln aller Serien und Filme die du anschaust[CR]- Synchronisiere deine gesammelten Serien und Filme zur Trakt Sammlung (direkt nach dem Bibliotheksupdate)[CR]- Automatisches aufräumen deiner Trakt Sammlung damit sie mit Kodi übereinstimmt[CR]- Halte gesehen Markierungen synchronisiert zwischen Kodi und Trakt[CR]- Bewerte Episoden und Filme direkt nach dem du sie geguckt hast[CR][CR]Besonderer Dank gilt allen die an diesem Plugin mit gearbeitet haben! Schau in die Commit Historie und das Änderungsprotokoll, um diese talentierten Entwickler zu sehen.</description>
        <description lang="el_GR">Αυτόματη κοινοποίηση στο Trakt.tv όλων των επεισοδίων και ταινιών που παρακολουθείτε! Μπορείτε να διατηρείτε αναλυτικό ιστορικό από ο,τιδήποτε είδατε, και να γίνετε μέρος μιας παγκόσμιας κοινότητας σινεφίλ και φαν της τηλεόρασης. Εγγραφείτε δωρεάν στο http://trakt.tv για ένα πλήθος παροχών:[CR][CR]- Αυτόματη κοινοποίηση όσων παρακολουθείτε[CR]- Εφαρμογές για κινητά iPhone, Android, Windows Phone και iPad[CR]- Μοιραστείτε ό,τι παρακολουθείτε (σε πραγματικό χρόνο), μαζί με τη βαθμολογία σας, στο facebook και το twitter[CR]- Προσωπικό ημερολόγιο, για να μη χάνετε ποτέ επεισόδιο[CR]- Ακολουθήστε τους φίλους σας, και άτομα για τα οποία ενδιαφέρεστε[CR]- Χρήση λιστών προβολής, για να μην ξεχνάτε τι θέλετε να δείτε[CR]- Εντυπωσιάστε τους φίλους σας με τις συλλογές σας[CR]- Δημιουργήστε προσωπικές λίστες με ό,τι θέμα επιθυμείτε[CR]- Δείτε την πρόοδό σας όσον αφορά τις τηλεοπτικές σειρές, με πολύ εύκολο τρόπο[CR]- Συγκρίνετε την πρόοδό σας με επίσημες λίστες, όπως των 250 Κορυφαίων του IMDb[CR]- Ανακαλύψτε νέες σειρές και ταινίες με βάση όσα έχετε ήδη παρακολουθήσει[CR]- Widget για την υπογραφή σας σε διάφορα forum[CR][CR]Τι μπορεί να κάνει αυτό το πρόσθετο;[CR][CR]- Αυτόματη κοινοποίηση όλων των επεισοδίων και ταινιών που παρακολουθείτε[CR]- Συγχρονισμός όλων των επεισοδίων και συλλογών ταινιών στο Trakt (αυτόματα μετά από κάθε ενημέρωση της συλλογής)[CR]- Αυτόματη εκκαθάριση της συλλογής σας στο Trakt ούτως ώστε να ταυτίζεται με αυτή στο Kodi[CR]- Συγχρονισμός όσων παρακολουθήσατε ήδη μεταξύ του Kodi και του Trakt[CR]- Βαθμολογήστε τις ταινίες και τα επεισόδια αφού τα παρακολουθήσετε[CR][CR]Ευχαριστούμε ιδιαιτέρως όλους όσους συνεισέφεραν σε αυτήν την εφαρμογή! Ελέγξτε το ιστορικό των προσθηκών και αλλαγών για να βρείτε αυτούς τους ταλαντούχους προγραμματιστές.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching to Trakt.tv! Keep a comprehensive history of everything you&apos;ve watched and be part of a global community of TV and movie enthusiasts. Sign up for a free account at http://trakt.tv and get a ton of features:[CR][CR]- Automatically scrobble what you&apos;re watching[CR]- Mobile apps for iPhone, iPad, Android, and Windows Phone[CR]- Share what you&apos;re watching (in real time) and rating to facebook and twitter[CR]- Personalized calendar so you never miss a TV show[CR]- Follow your friends and people you&apos;re interesed in[CR]- Use watchlists so you don&apos;t forget to what to watch[CR]- Track your media collections and impress your friends[CR]- Create custom lists around any topics you choose[CR]- Easily track your TV show progress across all seasons and episodes[CR]- Track your progress against industry lists such as the IMDb Top 250[CR]- Discover new shows and movies based on your viewing habits[CR]- Widgets for your forum signature[CR][CR]What can this addon do?[CR][CR]- Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching[CR]- Sync your TV episode and movie collections to Trakt (triggered after a library update)[CR]- Auto clean your Trakt collection so that it matches up with Kodi[CR]- Keep watched statuses synced between Kodi and Trakt[CR]- Rate movies and episode after watching them[CR][CR]Special thanks to all who contributed to this plugin! Check the commit history and changelog to see these talented developers.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">Haz scrobble automáticamente de todas tus Series de TV y Películas que estés viendo en Trakt.tv! Mantén un historial de todo lo que has visto y se parte de una comunidad global de entusiastas por las Series y Películas. Regístrate gratis en http://trakt.tv y consigue una tonelada de características:[CR][CR]- Scrobble automático de lo que estás viendo[CR]- Aplicaciones móviles para iPhone, iPad, Android y Windows Phone[CR]- Comparte lo que estás viendo (en tiempo real) y tu valoración en Facebook y Twitter[CR]- Calendario personalizado para que no te pierdas ninguna serie[CR]- Sigue tus amigos y personas de interés[CR]- Usa las watchlists para no olvidarte de lo que quieres ver[CR]- Controla tus colecciones multimedia e impresiona a tus amigos[CR]- Crea listas personalizadas sobre los temas de tu elección[CR]- Controla fácilmente el progreso de los episodios y temporadas de tus Series[CR]- Controla tu progreso en comparación con listas industriales como IMDb TOP 250[CR]- Descubre nuevas Series y Películas basadas en tus hábitos[CR]- Widgets para tu firma en foros[CR][CR]¿Qué puede hacer este add-on?[CR][CR]- Scrobble automático de las Episodios y Películas que estás viendo[CR]- Sincronizar tus colecciones Series y Películas con Trakt.tv (después de la actualización de la biblioteca)[CR]- Limpiar automáticamente tu colección de Trakt.tv para que sea idéntica a la de Kodi[CR]- Mantener el mismo estado de visionado entre Kodi y Trakt.tv[CR]- Valorar Películas y Episodios después de verlos[CR][CR]¡Un agradecimiento especial a todos los que han contribuido en este plugin! Revisa el histórico de commits y el histórico de cambios para ver todos esos desarrolladores con talento.</description>
        <description lang="et_EE">Talleta automaatselt kõik vaadatud episoodid ja filmid Trakt.tv teenuses! Oma kõikehõlmavat ajalugu kõigest vaadatust ja saa osa ülemaailmsest tele- ja filmihuviliste kogukonnast. Registreeri tasuta konto aadressil http://trakt.tv ja hangi palju funktsioone:[CR][CR]- Talleta automaatselt, mida vaatad[CR]- Mobiilirakendused iPhone, iPad, Android, ja Windows Phone tarbeks[CR]- Jaga seda, mida vaatad (reaalajas) ja hindeid Facebookis ja Twitteris[CR]- Isikupärastatud kalender, et sa ei magaks oma sarja kunagi maha[CR]- Jälgi oma sõpru ja inimesi, kellest oled huvitatud[CR]- Jälgimisloendite abil pead meeles, mis sarju vaatad[CR]- Jälgi oma meediakogusid ja avalda sõpradele muljet[CR]- Loo kohandatud loendid mis tahes valitud teemade kohta[CR]- Jälgi iga sarja hooaja ja episoodi vaatamise seisu[CR]- Sünkrooni oma vaatamisi filmitööstuse loendites nagu IMDb Top 250[CR]- Avasta oma vaatamisharjumuste põhjal uusi saateid ja filme[CR]- Vidinad, mida saad kasutada foorumi signatuuris[CR][CR]Mida see lisamoodul teeb?[CR][CR]- Talleta automaatselt kõik vaadatud episoodid ja filmid[CR]- Sünkrooni sarja- ja filmikogud teenusega Trakt (käivitub pärast meediakogu värskendamist)[CR]- Puhasta oma Trakti kogumik automaatselt, et see klapiks Kodiga[CR]- Sünkrooni Kodi ja Trakti vaatamiste olek[CR]- Rate movies and episode after watching them[CR][CR]Eriline tänu kõigile, kes selle lisamooduli loomisele kaasa aitasid! Need andekad arendajad leiab muudatuste logist.</description>
        <description lang="fi_FI">Kirjaa kaikki katsomasi sarjojen jaksot ja elokuvat Trakt.tv-kokoelmaasi automaattisesti! Säilytä kattava historia kaikesta katsomastasi ja osallistu maailmanlaajuiseen sarja- ja elokuvaharrastajien yhteisöön. Luo ilmainen tili osoitteessa http://trakt.tv ja hanki useita lisäominaisuuksia:[CR][CR]- Kirjaa automaattisesti mitä katsot[CR]- Mobiilisovellukset iPhone-, iPad-, Android- ja Windows Phone -alustoille[CR]- Jaa mitä katselet ja arvioit reaaliaikaisesti Facebookissa ja Twitterissä[CR]- Henkilökohtainen kalenteri, jotteivat sarjojen jaksot jää koskaan katsomatta[CR]- Seuraa kavereita ja kiinnostavia henkilöitä[CR]- Katselulistojen avulla et unohda mitä olit katsomassa[CR]- Seuraa mediakokoelmiasi ja tee vaikutus kavereihisi[CR]- Luo omia listoja mistä tahansa valitsemistasi aiheista[CR]- Pidä kirjaa sarjojen jokaisen kauden ja jakson katselutilanteesta[CR]- Pidä kirjaa katselutilanteestasi alan listoilla, kuten IMDb Top 250[CR]- Löydä uusia sarjoja ja elokuvia katselutottumustesi perusteella[CR]- Widgettejä, joita voit käyttää allekirjoituksissasi keskustelupalstoilla[CR][CR]Mitä tämä lisäosa tekee?[CR][CR]- Kirjaa automaattisesti kaikki sarja- ja elokuvakatselusi[CR]- Synkronoi sarja- ja elokuvakokoelmasi Trakt-kokoelmaasi (käynnistyy kirjastopäivityksen jälkeen)[CR] - Siivoaa Trakt-kokoelmasi automaattisesti vastaamaan Kodin kirjastoa[CR]- Synkronoi katselutilanteet Kodin ja Traktin välillä[CR] - Arvioi elokuvat ja jaksot niiden katselun päätyttyä helposti[CR][CR]Erityiskiitos lisäosan kehitykseen osallistuneille! Näet nämä lahjakkaat kehittäjät muutoshistoriasta.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">Scrobblez automatiquement sur Trakt.tv tous les épisodes TV et les films que vous regardez ! Gardez un historique complet de tout ce que vous avez regardé et prenez part à une communauté globale d&apos;amateurs de TV et de films. Enregistrez-vous avec un compte gratuit sur http://trakt.tv pour accéder à des tonnes de fonctionnalités : - Scrobbler automatiquement ce que vous regardez - Applications mobiles pour iPhone, iPad, Android et Windows Phone - Partager ce que vous regardez (en temps réel) et vos évaluations sur Facebook et Twitter - Calendrier personnalisé pour ne plus jamais rater un épisode - Suivez vos amis et les personnes qui vous intéressent - Utilisez des listes pour ne plus oublier ce que vous voulez regarder - Synchronisez vos collections de media pour impressionner vos amis - Créez des listes personnalisées autour des sujets que vous choisissez - Suivez facilement votre progression dans toutes les saisons et épisodes des séries TV - Comparez votre progression à des listes comme le Top 250 IMDb - Découvrez de nouvelles séries et de nouveaux films en vous basant sur vos habitudes de visionnage - Widget pour votre signature de forum Que fait cette extension ? - Scrobble automatiquement tous les épisodes TV et les films que vous regardez - Synchronise vos collections d&apos;épisodes TV et de films avec Trakt (déclenché après une mise à jour de la médiathèque) - Nettoie automatiquement votre collection Trakt pour qu&apos;elle concorde avec Kodi - Garde l&apos;état des visionnages synchronisé entre Kodi et Trakt - Note les films et épisodes après les avoir regardés Remerciements spéciaux à tous ceux qui ont apporté leur contribution à cette extension ! Allez faire un tour sur l&apos;historique des mises à jour et le journal des changements pour voir ces talentueux développeurs.</description>
        <description lang="he_IL">Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching to Trakt.tv! Keep a comprehensive history of everything you&apos;ve watched and be part of a global community of TV and movie enthusiasts. Sign up for a free account at http://trakt.tv and get a ton of features:[CR][CR]- Automatically scrobble what you&apos;re watching[CR]- Mobile apps for iPhone, iPad, Android, and Windows Phone[CR]- Share what you&apos;re watching (in real time) and rating to facebook and twitter[CR]- Personalized calendar so you never miss a TV show[CR]- Follow your friends and people you&apos;re interesed in[CR]- Use watchlists so you don&apos;t forget to what to watch[CR]- Track your media collections and impress your friends[CR]- Create custom lists around any topics you choose[CR]- Easily track your TV show progress across all seasons and episodes[CR]- Track your progress against industry lists such as the IMDb Top 250[CR]- Discover new shows and movies based on your viewing habits[CR]- Widgets for your forum signature[CR][CR]What can this addon do?[CR][CR]- Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching[CR]- Sync your TV episode and movie collections to Trakt (triggered after a library update)[CR]- Auto clean your Trakt collection so that it matches up with Kodi[CR]- Keep watched statuses synced between Kodi and Trakt[CR]- Rate movies and episode after watching them[CR][CR]Special thanks to all who contributed to this plugin! Check the commit history and changelog to see these talented developers.</description>
        <description lang="he_IL">Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching to Trakt.tv! Keep a comprehensive history of everything you&apos;ve watched and be part of a global community of TV and movie enthusiasts. Sign up for a free account at http://trakt.tv and get a ton of features:[CR][CR]- Automatically scrobble what you&apos;re watching[CR]- Mobile apps for iPhone, iPad, Android, and Windows Phone[CR]- Share what you&apos;re watching (in real time) and rating to facebook and twitter[CR]- Personalized calendar so you never miss a TV show[CR]- Follow your friends and people you&apos;re interesed in[CR]- Use watchlists so you don&apos;t forget to what to watch[CR]- Track your media collections and impress your friends[CR]- Create custom lists around any topics you choose[CR]- Easily track your TV show progress across all seasons and episodes[CR]- Track your progress against industry lists such as the IMDb Top 250[CR]- Discover new shows and movies based on your viewing habits[CR]- Widgets for your forum signature[CR][CR]What can this addon do?[CR][CR]- Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching[CR]- Sync your TV episode and movie collections to Trakt (triggered after a library update)[CR]- Auto clean your Trakt collection so that it matches up with Kodi[CR]- Keep watched statuses synced between Kodi and Trakt[CR]- Rate movies and episode after watching them[CR][CR]Special thanks to all who contributed to this plugin! Check the commit history and changelog to see these talented developers.</description>
        <description lang="hr_HR">Automatski sklobrajte sve TV epizode i filmove koje gledate na Trakt.tv! Vodite opsežnu povijest svega što ste gledali i budite dio globalne zajednice TV i filmskih entuzijasta. Prijavite se na besplatan račun na http://trakt.tv i dobijte mnogo značajki:[CR][CR]- Automatski skroblajte što gledate[CR]- Mobilne aplikacije za iPhone, iPad, Android, i Windows telefon[CR]- Dijelite što gledate (u stvarnom vremenu) i ocijenite na facebooku i twitteru[CR]- Personaliziran kalendar tako da nikada ne propustite TV emisiju[CR]- Slijedite svoje prijatelje i ljude koji vas zanimaju u[CR]- Koristite Popise gledanja tako da ne zaboravite što ste gledali[CR]- Pratite svoje medijske kolekcije i impresionirajte svoje prijateljte[CR]- Stvorite prilagođene popise o bili kojoj temi koju odaberete[CR]- Jednostavno pratite vaš napredak TV serije diljem svih sezona i epizoda[CR]- Pratite vaš napredak nasuprot industrijskih popisa poput IMDb Top 250[CR]- Otkrijete nove TV serije i filmove temeljene na vašim navikama gledanja[CR]- Widgeti za vaš potpis na forumu[CR][CR]Što sve može ovaj dodatak?[CR][CR]- Automatski skroblat sve TV epizode i filmove koje gledate[CR]- Uskladiti vaše TV epizode i filmske kolekcije na Trakt (pokrenuto nakon nadopune videoteke)[CR]- Automatsko čišćenje vaše Trakt kolekcije tako da se poklapa s Kodijem[CR]- Zadržava stanje gledanja usklađenim između Kodija i Trakta[CR]- Ocjenjuje filmove i epizode nakon gledanja[CR][CR]Posebno hvala svima koji su doprinijeli ovom dodatku! Provjerite povijest podneska i zapis promjena kako bi vidjeli te talentirane razvijatelje.</description>
        <description lang="hu_HU">Automatikusan átmásolja az összes TV epizódot és filmet, amit nézel a Trakt.tv-re! Tartsa meg az összes általad nézett sorozat részletes előzményeit, és légy része a tévé- és filmrajongók globális közösségének. Regisztrálj ingyenes fiókot a http://trakt oldalon. tv, és rengeteg funkciót kapsz: [CR][CR]- Automatikusan lekottázza, amit néztél[CR]- Mobilalkalmazások iPhone-ra, iPadre, Androidra, és Windows Phone[CR]- Megoszthatod, hogy mit nézel (valós időben) és milyen értékeléssel a facebookon és a twitteren[CR]- Személyre szabott naptár, hogy soha ne maradj le egy tévéműsorról sem[CR]- Kövesd barátaidat és azokat, akik iránt érdeklődsz[CR]- Használj nézési listákat, hogy ne felejtsd el, mit érdemes nézni[CR]- Kövesd nyomon a médiagyűjteményedet és nyűgözd le barátaidat[CR]- Egyéni listák létrehozása bármilyen témakörben[CR]- Könnyedén nyomon követheted a tévéműsorok előrehaladását az összes évad és epizód tekintetében[CR]- Nyomon követheted a fejlődésedet az iparági listákhoz képest, mint például az IMDb Top 250[CR]- Új műsorok és filmek felfedezése a nézési szokásaid alapján[CR]- Widgetek a fórum aláírásodhoz[CR][CR]Mit tud ez a bővítmény? [CR][CR]- Automatikusan lekottázhatja az összes TV epizódot és filmet, amit nézel[CR]- Szinkronizálhatja a TV epizód és film gyűjteményedet a Trakt-al (könyvtár frissítés után aktiválódik)[CR]- Automatikusan rendbe teheti a Trakt gyűjteményedet, hogy az egyezzen a Kodi-val[CR]- Szinkronizálja a megtekintett állapotokat a Kodi és a Trakt között[CR]- Értékelheted a filmeket és epizódokat a megtekintésük után[CR][CR]Külön köszönet mindenkinek, aki hozzájárult ehhez a pluginhez! Nézd meg a commit history-t és a changelog-ot, hogy lásd ezeket a tehetséges fejlesztőket.</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">Esegui automaticamente lo scrobbling di tutti gli episodi televisivi e dei film che guardi su Trakt.tv! Mantieni uno storico completo di tutto ciò che hai visto e prendi parte a una comunità globale di appassionati di TV e film. Registrati per avere un account gratuito su http://trakt.tv e ottieni una tonnellata di funzioni:[CR][CR]- Scrobbling automatico di quello che stai guardando[CR]- Applicazioni mobili per iPhone, iPad, Android e Windows Phone[CR]- Condividi su Facebook e Twitter ciò che guardi (in tempo reale) e la tua valutazione[CR]- Calendario personalizzato in modo da non perdere mai una puntata di uno show televisivo[CR]- Segui i tuoi amici e le persone che ti interessano[CR]- Usa la Watchlist in modo da non dimenticare cosa guardare[CR]- Tieni traccia delle tue raccolte multimediali e impressiona i tuoi amici[CR]- Crea liste personalizzate su qualsiasi argomento[CR]- Monitora facilmente i tuoi progressi nella visione degli show televisivi in tutte le stagioni ed episodi[CR]- Confronta i tuoi progressi con le liste di settore come la IMDb Top 250[CR]- Scopri nuovi spettacoli e film in base alle tue abitudini di visione[CR]- Widget per la firma del forum[CR][CR]Che cosa può fare questa add-on?[CR][CR]- Scrobble automatico di tutti gli episodi televisivi e film che vengono guardati[CR]- Sincronizzazione dei tuoi episodi TV e delle collezioni di film di Trakt (attivata dopo un aggiornamento della libreria)[CR]- Pulizia automatica della collezione Trakt in modo da farla corrispondere con Kodi[CR]- Mantenere lo stato delle visioni sincronizzate tra Kodi e Trakt[CR]- Votazione di ogni puntata o film dopo la visualizzazione[CR][CR]Un ringraziamento speciale a tutti coloro che hanno contribuito a questo plugin! Controllate la storia dei commit e la lista dei cambiamenti per vedere questi sviluppatori di talento.</description>
        <description lang="ko_KR">시청 중인 모든 TV 쇼 에피소드와 영화 정보를 자동으로 Trakt.tv에 전송합니다! 사용자가 시청한 모든 이력을 자세히 보관하고 전세계의 TV, 영화 커뮤니티의 일원으로 참여하세요. http://Trakt.tv에서 무료 회원으로 가입하고 다양한 기능을 활용하세요:[CR][CR]- 시청 중인 영화와 에피소드 정보를 자동으로 전송[CR]- iPhone, iPad, Android, Windows Phone 앱 지원[CR]- 시청 중 정보를 (실시간)으로 Facebook과 twitter로 공유하고 평가[CR]- 개인 캘린더로 TV 쇼 본방송을 놓치지 마세요[CR]- 친구와 관심있는 사람을 팔로우 하세요[CR]- 꼭 봐야 할 것들을 잊지 않기 위해 Watclist를 사용하세요[CR]- 여러분의 컬렉션을 관리하고 친구들을 감동 시키세요[CR]- 여러분이 선택한 모든 주제의 목록을 만드세요[CR]- 여러분의 TV 쇼 시청 진행 상태를 시즌별 에피소드별로 쉽게 기록하고 관리하세요[CR]- 여러분의 시청 상태를 IMDb Top 250 같은 목록과 비교해 보세요[CR]- 여러분이 시청한 자료를 토대로 새로운 영화와 TV쇼를 찾아보세요[CR]- 커뮤니티 포럼의 Widgets 으로 활용하세요[CR][CR]이 애든온이 할 수 있는 것은?[CR][CR]- 시청 중인 영화와 에피소드 정보를 자동으로 전송[CR]- 여러분의 TV 에피소드와 영화 컬렉션을 Trakt와 동기화 (라이브러리를 업데이트할 때 작동)[CR]- Kodi 라이브러리와 일치하도록 Trakt 컬렉션 자동 정리[CR]- Kodi와 Trakt 사이의 시청 정보 동기화[CR]- 영화와 에피소드를 시청한 후 평가하기[CR][CR]이 플러그인에 공헌한 모든 이에게 감사드립니다! 재능있는 이 개발자들을 확인하려면 커밋 이력과 변경사항을 확인하기 바랍니다.</description>
        <description lang="lt_LT">Automatiškai užregistruoti visus TV epizodus ir filmus, kuriuos žiūrite, Trakt.tv sistemoje! Laikykite išsamią istoriją visko, ką peržiūrėjote ir būkite globalios TV ir filmų entuziastų bendruomenės dalimi. Susikurkite nemokamą paskyrą http://trakt.tv puslapyje ir gaukite daugybę funkcionalumų:[CR][CR]- Automatiškai užregistruokite tai, ką žiūrite[CR]- Mobilios programelės, skirtos iPhone, iPad, Android ir Windows Phone[CR]- Dalinkitės tuo, ką žiūrite (realiuoju laiku) ir įvertinimais facebook ir twitter sistemose[CR]- Suasmenintas kalendorius, kad niekada nepraleistumėte TV laidos[CR]- Sekite savo draugus ir žmones, kuriais domitės[CR]- Naudokite peržiūros sąrašą, kad nepamirštumėte ką norite peržiūrėti[CR]- Sekite savo media kolekciją ir padarykite įspūdį savo draugams[CR]- Sukurkite savus sąrašus bet kokia pasirinkta tema[CR]- Lengvai sekite TV laidos progresą tarp visų sezonų ir epizodų[CR]- Sekite savo progresą tarp industrinių sąrašų, tokių kaip IMDb Top 250[CR]- Atraskite naujas laidas ir filmus pagal savo žiūrėjimo įpročius[CR]- Valdiklis jūsų forumo paskyros parašui[CR][CR]Ką gali šis priedas?[CR][CR]- Automatiškai registruoti visus TV epizodus ir filmus, kuriuos žiūrite[CR]- Sinchronizuoti jūsų TV epizodų ir filmų kolekciją su Trakt.tv (vykdoma po bibliotekos atnaujinimo)[CR]- Automatiškai išvalyti jūsų Trakt.tv kolekciją, kad ji sutaptų su Kodi[CR]- Išlaikyti peržiūrėjimo būsenas sinchronizuotas tarp Kodi ir Trakt.tv[CR]- Įvertinti filmus ir epizodus juos peržiūrėjus[CR][CR]Specialus ačiū visiems, kurie prisidėjo prie šio įskiepio! Patikrinkite kodo istoriją ir pakeitimų sąrašą, kad pamatytumėte šiuos talentingus kūrėjus.</description>
        <description lang="nl_NL">Scrobble automatisch alle TV afleveringen en films die je aan bekijken bent naar Trakt.tv! Hou een uitgebreide historie bij van alles wat je hebt bekeken en maak deel uit van een wereldwijde gemeenschap van TV- en filmliefhebbers. Schrijf je in voor een gratis account op http://trakt.tv en krijg een enorme hoeveelheid aan mogelijkheden:[CR][CR]- Automatisch scrobblen wat je aan het bekijken bent[CR]- Mobiele apps voor iPhone, iPad, Android en Windows Phone[CR]- Deel wat je aan het bekijken ben (gelijktijdig) en stuur je waardering door naar Facebook en Twitter[CR]- Persoonlijke kalender zodat je nooit een TV aflevering mist[CR]- Volg je vrienden en mensen waarin je ben geïnteresseerd[CR]- Gebruik kijklijsten zodat je niets mist van wat je wilt kijken[CR]- Leg je eigen mediaverzameling aan en maak indruk op je vrienden[CR]- Maak aangepaste lijsten over onderwerpen die je zelf kiest[CR]- Volg het verloop van je tv serie voor alle seizoenen en afleveringen[CR]- Vergelijk je bekeken films en series met bekende lijsten zoals de IMDb Top 250[CR]- Ontdek nieuwe series en films gebaseerd op jouw kijk gewoonten[CR]- Widgets voor jouw forum handtekening[CR][CR]Wat kan deze add-on doen?[CR][CR]- Automatisch scrobblen van alle TV afleveringen en films die je aan het bekijken bent[CR]- Synchroniseer je TV afleveringen en film collecties naar Trakt (start na een bibliotheekupdate)[CR]- Automatisch opschonen van je Trakt collectie zodat deze overeenkomt met Kodi[CR]- Houdt de bekeken status gesynchroniseerd tussen Kodi en Trakt[CR]- Geef een cijfer aan films en afleveringen na ze te hebben bekeken[CR][CR]Speciale dank aan allen die hebben meegeholpen met deze plugin! Bekijk de commentaar historie en wijzigingenlijst om deze getalenteerde ontwikkelaars te zien.</description>
        <description lang="pl_PL">Automatyczna rejestracja obejrzanych odcinków serialów i film w serwisie Trakt.tv! Przechowuj pełną historię wszystkich obejrzanych mediów i bądź częścią globalnej społeczności entuzjastów multimediów. Zarejestruj swoje konto za darmo na http://trakt.tv i uzyskaj dostęp do mnóstwa funkcji:[CR]- automatycznej rejestracji obejrzanych mediów[CR]- mobilnych aplikacji na iPhone&apos;a, iPada, Androida i Windows Phone[CR]- publikacji obejrzanych mediów i ich oceny (w czasie rzeczywistym) w serwisach Facebook i Twitter[CR]- osobistego kalendarza, żebyś nigdy nie przegapił emisji serialu[CR]- śledzenia aktywności znajomych i osób, którymi się interesujesz[CR]- listy pozycji do obejrzenia, żebyś nigdy nie zapomniał tego, co chcesz obejrzeć[CR]- udostępniania swojej kolekcji mediów, którą możesz zaimponować swoim znajomym[CR]- tworzenia niestandardowych list skupionych na wybranym temacie[CR]- łatwego śledzenia postępów oglądania sezonów i odcinków serialu[CR]- porównywania własnych postępów oglądania z publicznymi listami takimi jak lista Top 250 serwisu IMDb[CR]- odkrywanie nowych seriali i filmów na podstawie preferencji[CR][CR]Co potrafi ten dodatek?[CR][CR]- rejestrować automatycznie odtwarzania wszystkich odcinków seriali i filmów[CR]- synchronizację biblioteki filmów i odcinków seriali z kolekcją Trakt (uruchamianą po aktualizacji biblioteki)[CR]- czyszczenie kolekcji Trakt w celu pełnego dopasowania z biblioteką Kodi[CR]- utrzymywanie synchronizacji stanów obejrzenia między biblioteką Kodi a kolekcją Trakt[CR]- możliwość oceny filmów i odcinków seriali zaraz po obejrzeniu[CR][CR]Specjalne podziękowania dla wszystkich, którzy wnieśli swój wkład w tworzenie tego dodatku! Przejrzyj historię i dziennik zmian, aby poznać tych utalentowanych programistów.</description>
        <description lang="pt_PT">Automaticamente faça scrobble de filmes e séries que está a ver para o Trakt.tv! Mantenha um histórico de tudo o que visualizou e faça parte de uma comunidade de entusiastas de filmes e séries. Inscreva-se gratuitamente para uma conta em http://trakt.tv e receba uma tonelada de funcionalidades:[CR][CR]- Scrobble automático quando está a visualizar[CR]- Aplicações moveis para iPhone, iPad, Android, Windows Phone e Blackberry[CR]- Partilhe o que está a visualizar (em tempo real) e as suas classificações no facebook e twitter[CR]- Calendário personalizado de forma a nunca perder uma série[CR]- Siga os seus amigos e pessoas de interesse[CR]- Use listas para não esquecer o que ver[CR]- Mostre as suas bibliotecas de filmes e séries aos seus amigos[CR]- Crie listas personalizadas sobre os assuntos que quiser[CR]- Verifique que espisódios já visualizou e quais faltam ver[CR]- Veja que filmes tem do IMDB TOP 250[CR]- Descubra novos filmes e séries com base nos que já viu[CR]- Widgets para usar na assinatura de fóruns[CR][CR]O que pode este addon fazer?[CR]- Scrobble automático de todos os filmes e episódios de séries que está a ver[CR]- Sincronização dos filmes e episódios de séries vistos com o Trakt (após um update da biblioteca)[CR]- Limpeza automática do Trakt de forma a ficar igual ao Kodi[CR]- Manter as visualizações sincronizadas entre o Trakt e o Kodi[CR]- Classifique filmes e episódios após visualização[CR][CR]Um obrigado especial a todos os que contribuíram para este plugin! Veja o github e o changelog para ver quem são estes programadores talentosos.</description>
        <description lang="pt_PT">Automaticamente faça scrobble de filmes e séries que está a ver para o Trakt.tv! Mantenha um histórico de tudo o que visualizou e faça parte de uma comunidade de entusiastas de filmes e séries. Inscreva-se gratuitamente para uma conta em http://trakt.tv e receba uma tonelada de funcionalidades:[CR][CR]- Scrobble automático quando está a visualizar[CR]- Aplicações moveis para iPhone, iPad, Android, Windows Phone e Blackberry[CR]- Partilhe o que está a visualizar (em tempo real) e as suas classificações no facebook e twitter[CR]- Calendário personalizado de forma a nunca perder uma série[CR]- Siga os seus amigos e pessoas de interesse[CR]- Use listas para não esquecer o que ver[CR]- Mostre as suas bibliotecas de filmes e séries aos seus amigos[CR]- Crie listas personalizadas sobre os assuntos que quiser[CR]- Verifique que espisódios já visualizou e quais faltam ver[CR]- Veja que filmes tem do IMDB TOP 250[CR]- Descubra novos filmes e séries com base nos que já viu[CR]- Widgets para usar na assinatura de fóruns[CR][CR]O que pode este addon fazer?[CR]- Scrobble automático de todos os filmes e episódios de séries que está a ver[CR]- Sincronização dos filmes e episódios de séries vistos com o Trakt (após um update da biblioteca)[CR]- Limpeza automática do Trakt de forma a ficar igual ao Kodi[CR]- Manter as visualizações sincronizadas entre o Trakt e o Kodi[CR]- Classifique filmes e episódios após visualização[CR][CR]Um obrigado especial a todos os que contribuíram para este plugin! Veja o github e o changelog para ver quem são estes programadores talentosos.</description>
        <description lang="sk_SK">Automaticky synchronizujte informácie na Trakt.tv o všetkých seriáloch a filmoch ktoré sledujete.</description>
        <description lang="sv_SE">Skrobbla automatiskt alla TV-serie avsnitt och filmer du tittar på till Trakt.tv! Samla en innehållsrik historik om allt du tittar på och var en del av ett globalt kollektiv av TV och film entusiaster. Skapa ett gratis konto på http://trakt.tv och ta del av massor av funktioner.[CR][CR]- Skrobbla automatiskt vad du tittar på[CR]- Appar för iPhone, iPad, Android och Windows Phone[CR]- Dela vad du tittar på (i realtid) samt dina betyg på Facebook och Twitter[CR]- Personlig kalender så du aldrig missar en TV serie[CR]- Följ dina vänner och andra intressanta personer[CR]- Använd att se listor så du inte glömmer vad du skall se[CR]- Spåra dina media samlingar och imponera på dina vänner[CR]- Skapa listor för olika ämnen som du väljer[CR]- Spåra lätt hur mycket av en TV serie du sett, över alla säsonger och avsnitt[CR]- Jämför hur mycket film du har sett mot flera viktiga listor inom industrin, t.ex. IMDb Top 250[CR]- Upptäck nya TV serier och filmer baserat på din historik[CR]- Widgets för din forum signatur[CR][CR]Vad kan detta addon göra?[CR][CR]- Skrobbla automatiskt alla TV-serie avsnitt och filmer du tittar på[CR]- Synkronisera dina samlingar av film och Tv-serier till Trakt (startas efter en uppdatering av ditt bibliotek i Kodi)[CR]- Städa automatiskt din Trakt samling så den stämmer med Kodi.[CR]- Synkronisera sedd/osedd status mellan Kodi och Trakt[CR]- Betygsätt filmer och TV-serier avsnitt efter du har sett dem[CR][CR]Ett stort tack till alla som bidragit till detta plugin! Se loggen för tillägg och ändringar för att se vilka dessa talangfulla utvecklare är.</description>
        <description lang="uk_UA">Автоматично скробліть на Trakt.tv всі серіали та фільми, які ви переглядаєте! Ведіть повну історію ваших переглядів та станьте частиною міжнародної спільноти шанувальників кінематографу. Зареєструйте безкоштовний акаунт на http://trakt.tv та отримайте доступ до таких можливостей:[CR][CR]- Автоматичний скроблінг при перегляді[CR]- Мобільні додатки для iPhone, iPad, Android та Windows Phone[CR]- Діліться вашими переглядами та оцінками на facebook та twitter[CR]- Ваш персональний календар з яким ви ніколи не пропустите новий епізод улюбленого серіалу[CR]- Користуйтесь закладками щоб не забути що переглянути пізніше[CR]- Відстежуйте ваші медіа колекції та вразьте своїх друзів[CR]- Створюйте власні списки на будь-яку тему[CR]- Легко відстежуйте прогрес ваших серіалів, епізодів та сезонів[CR]- Відстежуйте прогрес перегляду найпопулярніших списків, таких як \\&quot;Топ 250 фільмів IMDb\\&quot;[CR]- Відривайте для себе нові серіали та фільми на основі ваших попередніх переглядів[CR] - Віджети для унікального банеру профіля на форумі[CR][CR]Що вміє цей додаток?[CR][CR]- Автоматично скроблити всі серіали та фільми які ви переглядаєте[CR]- Синхронізувати ваші колекції фільмів та серіалів до сервісу Trakt(спрацьовує при оновленні каталогу)[CR]- Автоматично очищати ваші Trakt колекції для синхронізації з локальним каталогом[CR]- Синхронізувати статус переглянутих між Kodi та Trakt[CR]- Оцінювати фільми та серіали після перегляду[CR][CR] Окрема подяка всім, хто долучився до розробки цього додатку! Огляньте історію змін щоб переглянути список цих талановитих розробників.</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">自动录制您正在观看的所有电视剧和电影到Trakt.tv！全面记录你看过的一切，成为全球电视和电影爱好者社区的一部分。在http://trakt.tv注册一个免费帐户，即可获得大量功能：[CR]；[CR]；-自动滚动您正在观看的内容[CR]；-iPhone、iPad、Android和Windows phone上的移动应用程序[CR]；-(实时)分享您正在观看的内容，并将其评分到Facebook和Twitter&amp;10；-个性化日历，让您永远不会错过任何电视节目[CR]；-关注您的朋友和您感兴趣的人&amp;使用观看列表，这样您就不会忘记要看什么。-跟踪您的媒体收藏并打动您的朋友[CR]；-围绕您选择的任何主题创建自定义列表[CR]；-轻松跟踪您的电视节目在所有季节和剧集中的进度-对照行业列表(如IMDB排名前250&amp;10；)跟踪您的进度-根据您的观看习惯发现新的剧集和电影[CR]；-用于论坛签名的小工具[CR]；[CR]；[CR]；[CR]；-自动滚动所有电视剧和电影。-将您的电视剧集和电影集同步到Trakt(在库更新后触发)[CR]；-自动清理您的Trakt集，以便它与Kodi&amp;10；匹配-保持在Kodi和Trakt&amp;10；之间同步的观看状态-在观看电影和集之后对它们进行评级[CR]；[CR]；特别感谢所有对此插件做出贡献的人！查看提交历史记录和更改日志，查看这些有才华的开发人员。</description>
    </extension>
</addon>
