<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="script.trakt" name="trakt" version="3.0.1" provider-name="trakt.tv">
	<requires>
		<import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
		<import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
		<import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.4.3"/>
		<import addon="script.module.six" version="1.7.3"/>
	</requires>
	<extension point="xbmc.python.script" library="script.py">
		<provides>executable</provides>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.service" name="trakt.service" library="default.py" start="login" />
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata" name="trakt.metadata">
		<summary lang="de">TV und Film Scrobbler für trakt.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="en">TV and movie scrobbler for trakt.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="en_US">TV and movie scrobbler for trakt.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="es">Scrobbler de Películas y Series para trakt.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="fr">Scrobbler TV et film pour trakt.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="lt">TV ir filmų registratorius, skirtas Trakt.tv</summary>
		<summary lang="pl">Dodatek umożliwiający rejestrację odtwarzanych i obejrzanych seriali i filmów w serwisie trakt.tv</summary>
		<description lang="en">Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching to trakt.tv! Keep a comprehensive history of everything you've watched and be part of a global community of TV and movie enthusiasts. Sign up for a free account at http://trakt.tv and get a ton of features:&#10;&#10;- Automatically scrobble what you're watching&#10;- Mobile apps for iPhone, iPad, Android, and Windows Phone&#10;- Share what you're watching (in real time) and rating to facebook and twitter&#10;- Personalized calendar so you never miss a TV show&#10;- Follow your friends and people you're interesed in&#10;- Use watchlists so you don't forget to what to watch&#10;- Track your media collections and impress your friends&#10;- Create custom lists around any topics you choose&#10;- Easily track your TV show progress across all seasons and episodes&#10;- Track your progress against industry lists such as the IMDb Top 250&#10;- Discover new shows and movies based on your viewing habits&#10;- Widgets for your forum signature&#10;&#10;What can this addon do?&#10;&#10;- Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching&#10;- Sync your TV episode and movie collections to trakt (triggered after a library update)&#10;- Auto clean your trakt collection so that it matches up with Kodi&#10;- Keep watched statuses synced between Kodi and trakt&#10;- Rate movies and episode after watching them&#10;&#10;Special thanks to all who contributed to this plugin! Check the commit history and changelog to see these talented developers.</description>
		<description lang="en_US">Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching to trakt.tv! Keep a comprehensive history of everything you've watched and be part of a global community of TV and movie enthusiasts. Sign up for a free account at http://trakt.tv and get a ton of features:&#10;&#10;- Automatically scrobble what you're watching&#10;- Mobile apps for iPhone, iPad, Android, and Windows Phone&#10;- Share what you're watching (in real time) and rating to facebook and twitter&#10;- Personalized calendar so you never miss a TV show&#10;- Follow your friends and people you're interesed in&#10;- Use watchlists so you don't forget to what to watch&#10;- Track your media collections and impress your friends&#10;- Create custom lists around any topics you choose&#10;- Easily track your TV show progress across all seasons and episodes&#10;- Track your progress against industry lists such as the IMDb Top 250&#10;- Discover new shows and movies based on your viewing habits&#10;- Widgets for your forum signature&#10;&#10;What can this addon do?&#10;&#10;- Automatically scrobble all TV episodes and movies you are watching&#10;- Sync your TV episode and movie collections to trakt (triggered after a library update)&#10;- Auto clean your trakt collection so that it matches up with Kodi&#10;- Keep watched statuses synced between Kodi and trakt&#10;- Rate movies and episode after watching them&#10;&#10;Special thanks to all who contributed to this plugin! Check the commit history and changelog to see these talented developers.</description>
		<description lang="es">Haz scrobble automáticamente de todas tus Series de TV y Películas que estés viendo en trakt.tv! Mantén un historial de todo lo que has visto y se parte de una comunidad global de entusiastas por las Series y Películas. Regístrate gratis en http://trakt.tv y consigue una tonelada de características:&#10;&#10;- Scrobble automático de lo que estás viendo&#10;- Aplicaciones móviles para iPhone, iPad, Android y Windows Phone&#10;- Comparte lo que estás viendo (en tiempo real) y tu valoración en Facebook y Twitter&#10;- Calendario personalizado para que no te pierdas ninguna serie&#10;- Sigue tus amigos y personas de interés&#10;- Usa las watchlists para no olvidarte de lo que quieres ver&#10;- Controla tus colecciones multimedia e impresiona a tus amigos&#10;- Crea listas personalizadas sobre los temas de tu elección&#10;- Controla fácilmente el progreso de los episodios y temporadas de tus Series&#10;- Controla tu progreso en comparación con listas industriales como IMDb TOP 250&#10;- Descubre nuevas Series y Películas basadas en tus hábitos&#10;- Widgets para tu firma en foros&#10;&#10;¿Qué puede hacer este add-on?&#10;&#10;- Scrobble automático de las Episodios y Películas que estás viendo&#10;- Sincronizar tus colecciones Series y Películas con trakt.tv (después de la actualización de la biblioteca)&#10;- Limpiar automáticamente tu colección de trakt.tv para que sea idéntica a la de Kodi&#10;- Mantener el mismo estado de visionado entre Kodi y trakt.tv&#10;- Valorar Películas y Episodios después de verlos&#10;&#10;¡Un agradecimiento especial a todos los que han contribuido en este plugin! Revisa el histórico de commits y el histórico de cambios para ver todos esos desarrolladores con talento.</description>
		<description lang="fr">Scrobble automatiquement sur trakt.tv tous les épisodes TV et les films que vous regarder! Garder un historique complet de tout ce que vous avez regardé et prenez part à une communauté globale d'amateurs de TV et de films. Enregistrez-vous pour un compte gratuit sur http://trakt.tv pour accéder à des tonnes de fonctionnalités:&#10;&#10;- Scrobblez automatiquement ce que vous regardez&#10;- Applications mobiles pour iPhone, iPad, Android et Windows Phone&#10;- Partagez ce que vous regardez (en temps réel) et vos notes sur Facebook et Twitter&#10;- Calendrier personnalisé pour ne plus jamais rater un épisode&#10;- Suivez vos amis et les gens qui vous intéressent&#10;- Utilisez des listes pour ne plus oublier ce que vous voulez regarder&#10;- Synchronisez vos collections de media et impressionnez vos amis&#10;- Créez des listes personnalisées autour des sujets que vous choisissez&#10;- Suivez facilement vos progrès pour toutes les saisons et épisodes des séries TV&#10;- Comparez vos progrès à des listes comme le Top 250 IMDb&#10;- Découvrez des nouvelles séries et des nouveaux films en vous basant sur vos habitudes de visionnement&#10;&#10;Que peut faire ce add-on?&#10;&#10;- Scrobbler automatiquement tous les épisodes TV et les films que vous regardez&#10;- Synchroniser vos collections d'épisodes TV et de films avec trakt (déclenché après une mise à jour de la médiathèque)&#10;- Nettoyer automatiquement votre collection trakt pour qu'elle concorde avec Kodi&#10;- Garder vos statuts de visionnement synchronisé entre Kodi et trakt&#10;- Noter les films et épisodes après les avoir regardés&#10;&#10;Remerciements spéciaux à tous ceux qui ont apporté leur contribution à ce plugin! Allez faire un tout sur l'historique des commits et le changelog pour voir ces talentueux développeurs.</description>
		<description lang="lt">Automatiškai užregistruoti visus TV epizodus ir filmus, kuriuos žiūrite, Trakt.tv sistemoje! Laikykite išsamią istoriją visko, ką peržiūrėjote ir būkite globalios TV ir filmų entuziastų bendruomenės dalimi. Susikurkite nemokamą paskyrą http://trakt.tv puslapyje ir gaukite daugybę funkcionalumų:&#10;&#10;- Automatiškai užregistruokite tai, ką žiūrite&#10;- Mobilios programelės, skirtos iPhone, iPad, Android ir Windows Phone&#10;- Dalinkitės tuo, ką žiūrite (realiuoju laiku) ir įvertinimais facebook ir twitter sistemose&#10;- Suasmenintas kalendorius, kad niekada nepraleistumėte TV laidos&#10;- Sekite savo draugus ir žmones, kuriais domitės&#10;- Naudokite peržiūros sąrašą, kad nepamirštumėte ką norite peržiūrėti&#10;- Sekite savo media kolekciją ir padarykite įspūdį savo draugams&#10;- Sukurkite savus sąrašus bet kokia pasirinkta tema&#10;- Lengvai sekite TV laidos progresą tarp visų sezonų ir epizodų&#10;- Sekite savo progresą tarp industrinių sąrašų, tokių kaip IMDb Top 250&#10;- Atraskite naujas laidas ir filmus pagal savo žiūrėjimo įpročius&#10;- Valdiklis jūsų forumo paskyros parašui&#10;&#10;Ką gali šis priedas?&#10;&#10;- Automatiškai registruoti visus TV epizodus ir filmus, kuriuos žiūrite&#10;- Sinchronizuoti jūsų TV epizodų ir filmų kolekciją su Trakt.tv (vykdoma po bibliotekos atnaujinimo)&#10;- Automatiškai išvalyti jūsų Trakt.tv kolekciją, kad ji sutaptų su Kodi&#10;- Išlaikyti peržiūrėjimo būsenas sinchronizuotas tarp Kodi ir Trakt.tv&#10;- Įvertinti filmus ir epizodus juos peržiūrėjus&#10;&#10;Specialus ačiū visiems, kurie prisidėjo prie šio įskiepio! Patikrinkite kodo istoriją ir pakeitimų sąrašą, kad pamatytumėte šiuos talentingus kūrėjus.</description>
		<description lang="pl">Automatyczna rejestracja obejrzanych odcinków serialów i film w serwisie trakt.tv! Przechowuj pełną historię wszystkich obejrzanych mediów i bądź częścią globalnej społeczności entuzjastów multimediów. Zarejestruj swoje konto za darmo na http://trakt.tv i uzyskaj dostęp do mnóstwa funkcji:&#10;- automatycznej rejestracji obejrzanych mediów&#10;- mobilnych aplikacji na iPhone'a, iPada, Androida i Windows Phone&#10;- publikacji obejrzanych mediów i ich oceny (w czasie rzeczywistym) w serwisach Facebook i Twitter&#10;- osobistego kalendarza żebyś nigdy nie przegapił emisji serialu&#10;- śledzenia aktywności znajomych i osób, którymi się interesujesz&#10;- korzystania z list odtwarzania żebyś nigdy nie zapomniał tego, co chcesz obejrzeć&#10;- udostępniania swojej kolekcji mediów, którą możesz zaimponować swoim znajomym&#10;- tworzenia niestandardowych list skupionych na wybranym temacie&#10;- łatwego śledzenia postępów oglądania sezonów i odcinków serialu&#10;- porównywania własnych postępów oglądania z publicznymi listami takimi jak lista Top 250 serwisu IMDb&#10;- odkrywanie nowych seriali i filmów na podstawie preferencji&#10;&#10;Co potrafi ten dodatek?&#10;&#10;- rejestrować automatycznie odtwarzania wszystkich odcinków seriali i filmów&#10;- synchronizację biblioteki filmów i odcinków seriali z kolekcją Trakt (uruchamianą po aktualizacji biblioteki)&#10;- czyszczenie kolekcji Trakt w celu pełnego dopasowania z biblioteką Kodi&#10;- utrzymywanie synchronizacji stanów obejrzenia między biblioteką Kodi a kolekcją Trakt&#10;- możliwość oceny filmów i odcinków seriali zaraz po obejrzeniu&#10;&#10;Specjalne podziękowania dla wszystkich, którzy wnieśli swój wkład w tworzenie tego dodatku! Przejrzyj historię i dziennik zmian, aby poznać tych utalentowanych programistów.</description>
		<language></language>
		<platform>all</platform>
		<forum>http://forum.kodi.tv/showthread.php?tid=138745</forum>
		<website>http://trakt.tv</website>
		<email></email>
		<source>https://github.com/trakt/script.trakt</source>
	</extension>
</addon>
